Streib, Victor; Papers apap330
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Case Files, 1947-2012, Undated; 1; 19 cubic ft.
  - Executed Women, United States, 1947-2008, Undated; 1.1; 4 cubic ft.
    - Louisiana: Slace, executed 1843-06-30, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Maine: general, 1947; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Maine: Mrs. Cornish, 1644, 1947; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Maine: Patience Sampson, ex, 1735-07-24, 1947; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Maryland: general, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Maryland: Esther Anderson, executed 1746-05-13, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Maryland: Mary Axwell, executed 1685-12-07, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - Maryland: Martha Bassett, executed 1752-01-19, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - Maryland: Judah, 1846, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - Maryland: Bess Beale, executed 1738-06-07, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - Maryland: Sarah Beavers, executed 1751, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - Maryland: Mary Burrass, executed 1723-10, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - Maryland: Margaret Caine, executed 1707, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - Maryland: Eleanor Carrah, executed 1723-05, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - Maryland: Aurelia chase, executed 1833-12-20, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - Maryland: Jenny Chase, executed 1755-07-04, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - Maryland: Judith Crawford, executed 1782-06-16, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - Maryland: Jenny Dashiell, executed 1821-10-19, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - Maryland: Eve, executed 1771-03-15, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - Maryland: Joan Colledge, executed 1669, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - Maryland: Mary Finmore, executed 1737-06-014, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - Maryland: Rebecca Fowler, executed 1685-10-09, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - Maryland: Grace Galloway, executed 1751-04-21, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - Maryland: Tida Glover, executed 1757-04-06, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - Maryland: Hannah, 1723-05, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - Maryland: Elizabeth Greene, executed 1660s, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - Maryland: Judith, executed 1741-03-31, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - Maryland: Henny, executed 1831-06, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - Maryland: Frances Horne, executed 1721-05, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - Maryland: Mary Jackson, executed 1727-03, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - Maryland: Elizabeth Jones, executed 1721-11, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - Maryland: Catherine Kieves, executed 1746, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - Maryland: Abigail Kimball, executed 1692, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)
    - Maryland: Kitty, executed 1821-03-02, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - Maryland: Mary Lunt, executed 1693-05, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - Maryland: Bridget Martin, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Maryland: Rebecca McCormick, executed 1859-06-24, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Maryland: Mary Naylor, executed 1863, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - Maryland: Kate Patapsco, executed 1805-05-08, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 93)
    - Maryland: Molly Pattison, executed 1742-04-28, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 94)
    - Maryland: Mary Perry, executed 1753, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 95)
    - Maryland: Judy Plater, executed 1739-03-30, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 96)
    - Maryland: Mary Powell, executed 1752-01-10, 1978; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 97)
    - Maryland: Lucy Purnell, executed 1868-02-28, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 98)
    - Maryland: Rachel, executed 1761-10-10, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 99)
    - Maryland: Mary Reed, executed 1723-05, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 100)
    - Maryland: Anne Robinson, executed 1722-10, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 101)
    - Maryland: Beck Smith, executed 1766-06-04, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 102)
    - Maryland: Betty Smith, executed 1764-06-20, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 103)
    - Maryland: Elizabeth Spurrier, executed 1713-11, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 104)
    - Maryland: Sarah Tracy, executed 1713-11, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 105)
    - Maryland: Elizabeth Williams, executed 1710-04, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 106)
    - Maryland: Isabella Yausley, executed 1671-04-17, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 107)
    - Maryland: Jenny, executed 1775-11-17, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 108)
    - Massachusetts: general, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 109)
    - Massachusetts: Esther Andrews, executed 1696-03-31, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 110)
    - Massachusetts: Susanna Andrews, executed 1696-03-31, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 111)
    - Massachusetts: Elizabeth Atwood, executed 1720-08-25, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 112)
    - Massachusetts: Alice Bishop, executed 1648, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 113)
    - Massachusetts: Bridget Bishop, executed 1692-06-10, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 114)
    - Massachusetts: Margaret Callogharne, executed 1715-06-13, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 115)
    - Massachusetts: Martha Carner, executed 1692-08-19, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 116)
    - Massachusetts: Rebecca Chambitt, executed 1733-09-27, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 117)
    - Massachusetts: Phillis Codman, executed 1755-09-18, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 118)
    - Massachusetts: Elizabeth Colson, executed 1727-05-27, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 119)
    - Massachusetts: Heppy Comfort, executed 1739-08-31, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 120)
    - Massachusetts: Abigail Converse, executed 1788-07-06, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 121)
    - Massachusetts: Martha Corey, executed 1692-09-22, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 122)
    - Massachusetts: Mary Dyer, executed 1660-06-01, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 123)
    - Massachusetts: Mary Easty, executed 1692-09-22, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 124)
    - Massachusetts: Elizabeth Emmerson, executed 1693-06-08, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 125)
    - Massachusetts: Morgan Fennison, executed 1743-04-24, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 126)
    - Massachusetts: Goody Glover, executed 1688-11-16, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 127)
    - Massachusetts: Sarah Good, executed 1692-09-22, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 128)
    - Massachusetts: Grace, executed 1693-06-08, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 129)
    - Massachusetts: Ann Hibben, executed 1656-06-19, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 130)
    - Massachusetts: Elizabeth How, executed 1692-07-19, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 131)
    - Massachusetts: Margaret Jones, executed 1648-06-15, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 132)
    - Massachusetts: Elizabeth Kendall, executed 1651, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 133)
    - Massachusetts: Alice Lake, executed 1684, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 134)
    - Massachusetts: Mary Latham, executed 1643-03-21, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 135)
    - Massachusetts: Marja Lambe, 1681, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 136)
    - Massachusetts: Mary Martin, executed 1647-03-18, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 137)
    - Massachusetts: SusannahMartin, executed 1692-07-19, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 138)
    - Massachusetts: Rebecca Nurse, executed 1692-07-19, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 139)
    - Massachusetts: Alice Parker, executed 1692-09-22, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 140)
    - Massachusetts: Mary Parker, executed 1692-09-22, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 141)
    - Massachusetts: Mary Parsons, executed 1651-05-29, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 142)
    - Massachusetts: Phyllis, executed 1751-05-16, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 143)
    - Massachusetts: Hannah Piggen (Pigeon), executed 1785-07-21, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 144)
    - Massachusetts: Ann Pudeater, executed 1692-09-22, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 145)
    - Massachusetts: Wilmot Read, executed 1692-09-22, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 146)
    - Massachusetts: Esther Rodgers, executed 1701-07-15, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 147)
    - Massachusetts: Margaret Scott, executed 1692-09-22, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 148)
    - Massachusetts: Slave, executed 1749, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 149)
    - Massachusetts: Slave, executed 1758, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 150)
    - Massachusetts: Sarah Smith, executed 1698-08-25, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 151)
    - Massachusetts: Bathsheba Ruggles Spooner, executed 1778-07-02, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 152)
    - Massachusetts: Dorothy Talby, executed 1638-12, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 153)
    - Massachusetts: Sarah Three needles, executed 1698-11-17, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 154)
    - Massachusetts: Unknown Woman, executed 1721-05-21, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 155)
    - Massachusetts: Unknown Woman, executed 1837-08-31, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 156)
    - Massachusetts: Elizabeth Wakefield, executed 1747-10-08, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 157)
    - Massachusetts: Rachel Wall, executed 1789-10-08, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 158)
    - Massachusetts: Sarah Wild, executed 1692-07-19, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 159)
    - Massachusetts: Betty Winslow, executed 1712-05-07, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 160)
    - Michigan: Indian Slave Woman, executed 1763-02, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 161)
    - Michigan: Ann Wyley, executed 1777-03-26, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 162)
    - Minnesota: Maryann Evards Wright Bilansky, executed 1860-03-23, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 163)
    - Mississippi: general, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 164)
    - Mississippi: Martha, executed 1852-06-18, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 165)
    - Mississippi: Maria, executed 1848, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 166)
    - Mississippi: Anarchy, executed 1852-02-22, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 167)
    - Mississippi: Sue, executed 1851-11-28, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 168)
    - Mississippi: Eliza, executed 1858-06-11, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 169)
    - Mississippi: Cicely, executed 1850-05-24, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 170)
    - Mississippi: Eliza, executed 1838-08-10, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 171)
    - Mississippi: Mily Fox, executed 1851-06-14, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 172)
    - Mississippi: Clarissa (Claracy), executed 1849-05-11, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 173)
    - Mississippi: Mary Holmes, executed 1937-04-29, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 174)
    - Mississippi: Mildred Louise James Johnson, executed 1944-05-19, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 175)
    - Mississippi: Ann Knight, executed 1922-08-11, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 176)
    - Mississippi: Slave, executed 1863, 1985; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 177)
    - Mississippi: Nancy, executed 1833-12-06, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 178)
    - Mississippi: Adaline, executed 1848-10-27, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 179)
    - Mississippi: Pattie Perdue, executed 1922-01-13, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 180)
    - Mississippi: Mary Jane, executed 1854-07-28, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 181)
    - Missouri: general, 1997; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 182)
    - Missouri: Mary Andrews, executed 1834-04-30, 1997; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 183)
    - Missouri: America, executed 1843-06-10, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 184)
    - Missouri: Mary Brinker, executed 1838-09-30, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 185)
    - Missouri: Celia, executed 1855-12-21, 1983; 1996; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 186)
    - Missouri: Slave Woman, executed 1839-05-14, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 187)
    - Missouri: Susan, executed 1844-11-23, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 188)
    - Missouri: Annice, executed 1828-08-23, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 189)
    - Missouri: Unknown Indian, executed 1887-05, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 190)
    - Nevada: Elizabeth Atherton Potts, executed 1890-06-20, 1981; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 191)
    - New Hampshire: general, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 192)
    - New Hampshire: Ruth Blay, executed 1768-12-30, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 193)
    - New Hampshire: Penelope Kenny, executed 1739-12-27, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 194)
    - New Hampshire: Sarah Simpson, executed 1739-12-27, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 195)
    - New Jersey: general, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 196)
    - New Jersey: Christina Bell, executed 1721, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 197)
    - New Jersey: Belle, executed 1783, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 198)
    - New Jersey: black girl, executed 1845, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 199)
    - New Jersey: Anne Buzard, executed 1754-07-13, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 200)
    - New Jersey: Mary Cole, executed 1812-06-26, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 201)
    - New Jersey: Unidentified Slave, executed 1755, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 202)
    - New Jersey: Bridget Deigan, executed 1867-08-30, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 203)
    - New Jersey: Elizabeth (Eliza) Freeman, executed 1832-07, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 204)
    - New Jersey: Hagar, 1717, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 205)
    - New Jersey: Jane Huff, executed 1837-05-28, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 206)
    - New Jersey: Dine McDonald, executed 1788-10-17, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 207)
    - New Jersey: Margaret Meierhoffer, executed 1881-01-08, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 208)
    - New Jersey: Slave, executed 1765-12-30, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 209)
    - New Jersey: Slave, executed 1825, 1982; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 210)
    - New jersey: Maria Stuart, executed 1826-09, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 211)
    - New Jersey: Elizabeth Vaughn, executed 1766-06-02, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 212)
    - New Jersey: Jemmina Westerdon, executed 1730, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 213)
    - New Mexico: Paula Angel, executed 1861-04-26, 1998; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 214)
    - New Mexico: Maria Fancesca Cochiti, executed 1779-01-26, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 215)
    - New Mexico: Maria Josepa Cochita, executed 1779-01-26, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 216)
    - New York: general, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 217)
    - New York: Mary Antoine, executed 1814-09-03, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 218)
    - New York: Anna Antonio, executed 1934-08-09, 1985; 1986; 2001; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 219)
    - New York: Martha Beck, executed 1951-03-08, 1986; 2001; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 220)
    - New York: Slave, executed 1794-03-14, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - New York: Ann Bowern, executed 1708-03-24, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - New York: Catharine Bronson, executed 1767 or 1768, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - New York: Dayon, executed 1803-07-08, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - New York: Rose Butler, executed 1819-07-09, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - New York: Catharine Cashiere, executed 1829-05-07, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - New York: Elizabeth Clarke, executed 1767 or 1768, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - New York: Eva Goo, executed 1935-06-27, 1985; 2001; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - New York: Slave, executed 1774, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - New York: Mary Creighton, executed 1936-07-16, 1986; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - New York: Mary Daily, rx. 1771-05-10, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - New York: Dean, executed 1794-03-14, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - New York: Elizabeth Dent, executed 1766, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - New York: Dinah, executed 1793-11-27, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - New York: Roxana Druse, executed 1887-02-28, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - New York: Peggy Facto (Facteau), executed 1825-03-18, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - New York: Mary Farmer, executed 1909-03-29, 1986; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - New York: Elizabeth Floyd, executed 1766-11, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - New York: Helen Fowler, executed 1944-11-16, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - New York: Negro Woman, executed 1775-01-01, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - New York: Margaret Grass, executed 1736-10, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - New York: Deborah Gryce, executed 1714-12-17, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - New York: Angel Hendricks, executed 1669-07-17, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - New York: Ann Hoag, executed 1852-07-30, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - New York: Bett, executed 1748-07-23, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - New York: Margaret Houghtaling, executed 1817-10-17, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - New York: Sarah Hughson, executed 1741, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - New York: Margaret Kerry, executed 1741-06-12, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - New York: Frances Malone, executed 1767-11-23, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - New York: Mary, executed 1706-09-13, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - New York: Sitty, executed 1774-03-30, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - New York: Nelly, executed 1790-10-15, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - New York: Martha Place, executed 1899-03-20, 1986; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - New York: Mary Runkle, executed 1847-11-09, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - New York: Sarah, executed 1712, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - New York: Diana Sellick, executed 1817-04-18, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - New York: Mary Siggins, executed 1771, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - New York: Slave, executed 1708-02-02, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - New York: Slave, 1771, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - New York: Ruth Brown Snyder, executed 1928-01-12, 1985; 1991; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - New York: Venus, executed 1767-02-09, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - New York: Mary Yates, executed 1765-02-08, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - New York: Barbara Stillwell, executed 1784-06-22, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - New York: Hannah Travis, executed 1720, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - New York: Woman, executed 1716 or 1717, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - New York: Woman, executed 1737-09-07, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - New York: Elizabeth Van Valkenburgh, executed 1846-01-24, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - North Carolina: Velma Barfeld, executed 1984-11-02, 1985; 1991; 1999; 2008; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - North Carolina: Matilda Carter, executed 1882-01-13, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - North Carolina: Magdalen Collar, 1720, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - North Carolina: Amy Dodson, executed 1832-07-28, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - North Carolina: Esther, executed 1779-04, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - North Carolina: Fanny, executed 1857-03-27, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - North Carolina: Harriet, executed 1780-11-18, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - North Carolina: Jenny, executed 1780-11-18, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - North Carolina: Slave, executed 1805-07-13, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - North Carolina: Margarette, executed 1849-05-25, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - North Carolina: Massy, executed 1857-05-08, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - North Carolina: Molly, executed 1828-06-20, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - North Carolina: Myham, executed 1806-03-28, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - North Carolina: Ormond, executed 1770-07, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - North Carolina: Rosanna Lightner Phillips, executed 1943-01-01, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - North Carolina: Rose, executed 1766, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - North Carolina: Rose, executed 1783, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - North Carolina: Caroline Shipp, executed 1892-01-22, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - North Carolina: Frankie Silver, executed 1833-07-12, 2008; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - North Carolina: Catharine Sullivan, executed 1738, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - North Carolina: Slave, executed 1770, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - North Carolina: Bessie May Williams, executed 1944-12-29, 1984; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - North Carolina: Slave, executed 1861-02-23, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - Ohio: Betty Butler, executed 1954-06-12, 1985; 2002; 2004; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - Ohio: Dovie Smarr Dean, executed 1954-01-15, 1985; 1998; 2004; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - Ohio: Ester Foster, executed 1844-02-09, 2005; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - Ohio: Anna Marie Hahn, executed 1938-12-07, 1985; 2004; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - Ohio: Anna Marie Hahn, executed 1938-12-07, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - Oklahoma: Wanda Jean Allen, executed 2001-01-11, 1991 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - Oklahoma: Wanda Jean Allen, executed 2001-01-11, 1990; 2005; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - Oklahoma: Marilyn Kay Plantz, executed 2001-05-01, 1992 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - Oklahoma: Marilyn Kay Plantz, executed 2001-05-01, 1989; 2005; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - Oklahoma: Lois Nadean Smith, executed 2001-12-04, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - Oklahoma: Lois Nadean Smith, executed 2001-12-14, 1990; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - Pennsylvania: General, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - Pennsylvania: Chloe, executed 1801-07-18, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - Pennsylvania: Sarah Clark, executed 1799-10-30, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - Pennsylvania: Catherine Conner, executed 1737-07-02, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - Pennsylvania: susannah Cox, executed 1809-06-10, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - Pennsylvania: Elizabeth, executed 1774-04-30, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)